[{"answer": "I was actually in the south side of Oklahoma City when I'd seen the tornado.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "You survived the tornado, then what?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "He had a couple of ribs broken.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "What condition was he in when you were able to physically get to him?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "ORGAN: And Jerrel, who is this man, do you know?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "ALEY: I believe so.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "And do you know if they're extending the same principle to other people who may have been in your position?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Can we see it?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "How bad have we landed you in it?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Is it set right there?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "My name is Michelle Alain.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "And what's your -- what's your name?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "We are doing wonderful.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "How are you all doing as a family?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "It was just --", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "What was it like for you, Jordan, to actually experience a tornado that big?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Well, before, you know -- before the tornado hit, I could tell by just looking at it from how close it was that this is not the kind of tornado or storm that you want to be above ground for.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Did you fear at one stage that you may not all come out alive?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Yes, they were taking random pictures of the storm debris, and things, and inside one of these pictures she happened to notice the vehicle that we had described.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "And they saw the car in the picture and posted it on Facebook, right?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Is that your understanding, Congressman?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Well, most of the newer schools actually do have safe rooms in them that are added automatically.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Why is that, and what will happen in light of what's happened here?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "It's -- thank you, Piers.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "What has it been like on the ground there?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well, thank the Lord, OU is supplying housing here for us.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "What are you doing for accommodations for your family?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I was -- I had gone to Norman yesterday morning while Lindsey and Jeremiah were out there.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What was your reaction, RJ, when you realized that Phoebe had survived after you had given up all hope?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I don't know how far it came.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "But you believe that it must have traveled through the air for up to 40 or 50 acres, is that right?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Honestly, I just quickly saw it, and my mission was to get the kids out and to look to assess what injuries we had.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "What did you think when you saw this horse, standing there alive?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "They're all doing well.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "How are they all doing?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I have a cracked rib and some stitches on my back.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "What happened to you?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "I am still shaken up.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "How are you feeling about it all?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "It was -- it was amazing.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Well, the most valuable thing you have in the world is your memory.", "docId": "130522pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "The people who have lost loved ones in Oklahoma, particularly ones who have lost their kids and so on, what is the best advice that you've learned, maybe for yourself, that you could offer them?", "qSentId": 662}]